A Register of the Records of the Russkaia sredniaia shkola (Paris, France)Records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Office file, 1920-1997 and undated. (Box 1)
  - Student records
    - Krotkova, Nadezhda (Folder 22: 61)
    - Kruglik-Oshchevskaia, Kseniia (Folder 22: 62)
    - Krundishev, Ivan (Folder 22: 63)
    - Kruntsevich, Susanna (Folder 22: 64)
    - Krupnikov, Grigorii (Folder 22: 65)
    - Krupnikov, Il'ia (Folder 22: 66)
    - Krutikova, Nina (Folder 22: 67)
    - Krylatov, Dimitrii (Folder 22: 68)
    - Kryzhanovskii, Vadim (Folder 22: 69)
    - Krzhivoblotskii, Georgii (Folder 22: 70)
    - Kube, Oleg (Folder 22: 71)
    - Kuchenkov, Aleksei (Folder 22: 72)
    - Kucherenko, Mikhei (Folder 22: 73)
    - Kudriakov, Ivan, and Liubov', and Sergei, and Vladimir (Folder 22: 74)
    - Kudriashev, Georgii (Folder 22: 75)
    - Kudriavtseva, Kira (Folder 22: 76)
    - Kuklovskii, Iurii (Folder 22: 77)
    - Kukol'-Iasnopol'skii, Sergei (Folder 22: 78)
    - Kulakov, Aleksandr, and Mikhail (Folder 22: 79)
    - Kuliabko-Koretskaia, Elizaveta (Folder 22: 80)
    - Kulikovskii, Gurii, and N., and Tikhon (Folder 22: 81)
    - Kumshatskaia, Irina (Folder 22: 82)
    - Kurdiukov, Ioann, and Liubov', and Sergii, and Vladimir (Folder 22: 83)
    - Kurieva, Lila (Folder 22: 84)
    - Kurilenko, C. (Folder 22: 85)
    - Kurisis, Rashel' (Box-folder 23: 1)
    - Kurlin, Georgii (Folder 23: 2)
    - Kushkovskii, Iaroslav, and Rostislav (Folder 23: 3)
    - Kustovskii, Valentin (Folder 23: 4)
    - Kutsin, Viktor (Folder 23: 5)
    - Kuzin, Nikolai, and Oleg (Folder 23: 6)
    - Kuzmichev, Konstantin, and Nadezhda, and Vera (Folder 23: 7)
    - Kuz'min, Vladimir (Folder 23: 8)
    - Kuz'minskii, Igor' (Folder 23: 9)
    - Kuznetsov, Aleksandr, Georgii (Folder 23: 10)
    - Kuznetsova, Anna (Folder 23: 11)
    - Labushniak, Fotii (Folder 23: 12)
    - Ladrinovskaia, Ekaterina (Folder 23: 13)
    - Laek, Platon, de (Folder 23: 14)
    - Lagodovskaia, Marina (Folder 23: 15)
    - Lagan'e, Lena (Folder 23: 16)
    - Lalovich, Ol'ga (Folder 23: 17)
    - Lamsdorf, Grigorii, Nikolai (Folder 23: 18)
    - Lanshon, Dominique, Elizaveta (Folder 23: 19)
    - Lapkin, Nikolai (Folder 23: 20)
    - Laptev, Aleksandr (Folder 23: 21)
    - Larionov, Georgii (Folder 23: 22)
    - Larina-Starzhenetskaia, Irina (Folder 23: 23)
    - Latsis, Diia (Folder 23: 24)
    - Laura, Aleksandr (Folder 23: 25)
    - Laureillard, Jacques (Folder 23: 26)
    - Lavrinenko, Leonid (Folder 23: 27)
    - Lavrov, Oleg (Folder 23: 28)
    - Lavrukhina, Nina (Folder 23: 29)
    - Lazarev, Vladimir (Folder 23: 30)
    - Lazareva, Nataliia (Folder 23: 31)
    - Lazarevskii, Ivan, and Petr, and Sylvia (Folder 23: 32)
    - Lebedev, Andrei (Folder 23: 33)
    - Lebedev, Iurii, and Liudmila, and Tat'iana (Folder 23: 34)
    - Lebedeva, Elizaveta (Folder 23: 35)
    - Lebedeva, Irina (Folder 23: 36)
    - Lebedeva, Liubov' (Folder 23: 37)
    - Lebedeva, Liudmila (Folder 23: 38)
    - Lebedeva, Mariia (Folder 23: 39)
    - Lebengaupt, Al'ma (Folder 23: 40)
    - Lebedintsev, Aleksandr, and Mikhail (Folder 23: 41)
    - Le Clercq, Petr (Folder 23: 42)
    - Ledkovskii-Tamm, Nikolai (Folder 23: 43)
    - Lefevre, Irina (Folder 23: 44)
    - Lekhovskii, Zakharii (Folder 23: 45)
    - Lekok, Vera (Folder 23: 46)
    - Lelianova, Elena (Folder 23: 47)
    - Leman, Nadezhda (Folder 23: 48)
    - Lemeny-Makedone, Aleksei de, and Liubov' de, and Nikolai de (Folder 23: 49)
    - Lemke, Igor' (Folder 23: 50)
    - Lents, Vera (Folder 23: 51)
    - Leont'ev, Konstantin (Folder 23: 52)
    - Leper, Aleksandr (Folder 23: 53)
    - Lermontova, Anna (Folder 23: 54)
    - Leshchinskii, Daniil (Folder 23: 55)
    - Leshchinskii, Petr (Folder 23: 56)
    - Lesli, Sofiia (Folder 23: 57)
    - Levchenko, Aleksandra (Folder 23: 58)
    - Levich, Boris (Folder 23: 59)
    - Levinson-Levina, Mirra (Folder 23: 60)
    - Levitskii, Marina, and Vsevolod (Folder 23: 61)
    - Levshin, Irina, and Vasilii (Folder 23: 62)
    - Liakov, Aleksandr (Folder 23: 63)
    - Liakhov, Dimitrii (Folder 23: 64)
    - Liashkov, Mikhail (Folder 23: 65)
    - Liaskovskii, Mariia, and Petr (Folder 23: 66)
    - Liber, Mikhail (Folder 23: 67)
    - Lidle, Fedor (Folder 23: 68)
    - Lidval, Leonard (Folder 23: 69)
    - Likhachev, Aleksandr (Folder 23: 70)
    - Likhtenshtein, Mr., and Kseniia (Folder 23: 71)
    - Likhvintseva, Anna (Folder 23: 72)
    - Lindenwald, Vladimir (Folder 23: 73)
    - Lipin, Aleksei (Folder 23: 74)
    - Liquier, Ivan (Folder 23: 75)
    - Lisenko, Erast, and Ol'ga (Folder 23: 76)
    - Lishin, Dimitrii (Folder 23: 77)
    - Lisim, Georgii, and Nataliia (Folder 23: 78)
    - Lisovets, Petr (Folder 23: 79)
    - Litvinov, Andrei (Folder 23: 80)
    - Litvinova, Irina (Folder 23: 81)
    - Liubenets, Anastasiia, Pavel (Folder 23: 82)
    - Liusman, Andrei (Box-folder 24: 1)
    - Liutuiskaia, Evgeniia, and Nina (Folder 24: 2)
    - Liuzin'en, Vladimir (Folder 24: 3)
    - Liven, Irina (Folder 24: 4)
    - Lobov, Iurii (Folder 24: 5)
    - Lodyzhenskaia, Elena (Folder 24: 6)
    - Lodyzhenskaia, Ol'ga (Folder 24: 7)
    - Lodyzhenskii, Aleksei, and Marina (Folder 24: 8)
    - Lokhanskaia, Tamara (Folder 24: 9)
    - Loktev, Gavriil (Folder 24: 10)
    - Lomakina, Tat'iana (Folder 24: 11)
    - Lomar, Francoise (Folder 24: 12)
    - Lopatinskii, Igor', and Oleg (Folder 24: 13)
    - Lopato, Georgii, and Liudmila (Folder 24: 14)
    - Lopukhina, Marina (Folder 24: 15)
    - Lopukhin, Rafail (Folder 24: 16)
    - Lopukhin, Sergei (Folder 24: 17)
    - Luchaninov, Sergei (Folder 24: 18)
    - Luchinskaia, Ol'ga (Folder 24: 19)
    - Lugin-Shevchenko, Mr. (Folder 24: 20)
    - Lukas, Dominik (Folder 24: 21)
    - Lukianova, Evdokiia, and Mariia (Folder 24: 22)
    - Luk'ianskii, Dimitrii (Folder 24: 23)
    - Lukin, Mikhail (Folder 24: 24)
    - Lund, Kseniia, and Liudmila (Folder 24: 25)
    - Lunin, Dimitrii, and Vladimir (Folder 24: 26)
    - Luppov, Igor' (Folder 24: 27)
    - Lur'e, Didier (Folder 24: 28)
    - Lur'e, Sergei (Folder 24: 29)
    - Lyzlov, Aleksandr, Iurii, Zoia (Folder 24: 30)
    - L'vova, Mariia (Folder 24: 31)
    - L'vovich-Kostrits, Irina (Folder 24: 32)
    - Maevskaia, Elizaveta, and Vera (Folder 24: 33)
    - Maiboroda, Andrei (Folder 24: 34)
    - Maidanovich, Elena, and Irina, and Nataliia, and Tat'iana (Folder 24: 35)
    - Maidanovskaia, Irina (Folder 24: 36)
    - Maier, Georgii (Folder 24: 37)
    - Maier, Kirill (Folder 24: 38)
    - Maier, Teodor (Folder 24: 39)
    - Mailov, Armand, and Irina, and Lazar' (Folder 24: 40)
    - Makarenko, Nikita, and Ol'ga (Folder 24: 41)
    - Makarovskii, Mikhail (Folder 24: 42)
    - Makovetskaia, Svetlana (Folder 24: 43)
    - Makovskii, I. (Folder 24: 44)
    - Maksheeva, Nadezhda, and Vera (Folder 24: 45)
    - Maler, Georgii, and Kira, and Valeriia (Folder 24: 46)
    - Malov, Igor' (Folder 24: 47)
    - Maksimova, Nadezhda (Folder 24: 48)
    - Malakhov, Ivan (Folder 24: 49)
    - Maliarchuk, Nina (Folder 24: 50)
    - Malikonian, Elena (Folder 24: 51)
    - Malinin, Konstantin, and Marianna (Folder 24: 52)
    - Malizhenovskaia, Aleksandra (Folder 24: 53)
    - Malkin, Zinaida (Folder 24: 54)
    - Maloletenkov, Nina, and Sergei (Folder 24: 55)
    - Mal'tseva, Elena (Folder 24: 56)
    - Mal'tseva, Ekaterina (Folder 24: 57)
    - Mal'tsev, Mikhail (Folder 24: 58)
    - Mamontov, Kirill (Folder 24: 59)
    - Mamontova, Tat'iana (Folder 24: 60)
    - Mandel'shtam, Iurii, Pavel, Tat'iana (Folder 24: 61)
    - Mandenov, Boris (Folder 24: 62)
    - Mantashev, Aleksandr (Folder 24: 63)
    - Manuchareva, Svetlana, and Tamara (Folder 24: 64)
    - Marin, Iuliia (Folder 24: 65)
    - Marinesko, Nadezhda (Folder 24: 66)
    - Markova, Kira (Folder 24: 67)
    - Markova, Ol'ga (Folder 24: 68)
    - Martem'ianova, Galina (Folder 24: 69)
    - Martyniuk, Evgenii (Folder 24: 70)
    - Marsant, Igor' (Folder 24: 71)
    - Marshalk, Georgii (Folder 24: 72)
    - Mashtaler, Kseniia, and Vladimir (Folder 24: 73)
    - Masianov, Aleksei (Folder 24: 74)
    - Maslikov, Konstantin (Folder 24: 75)
    - Mateo, Ekaterina, and Ivan (Folder 24: 76)
    - Materno, Iustin (Folder 24: 77)
    - Matrosova, Mariia, Tat'iana (Folder 24: 78)
    - Mazankin, Sviatoslav (Folder 24: 79)
    - Medler, Erik (Folder 24: 80)
    - Medvedev, Dimitrii, Svetlana (Folder 24: 81)
    - Medvedev, Nikolai (Folder 24: 82)
    - Medvedev, Sergei (Folder 24: 83)
    - Medvedeva, Liudmila (Folder 24: 84)
    - Medynskaia, Ol'ga (Box-folder 25: 1)
    - Medyntsev, Nikolai (Folder 25: 2)
    - Medyntseva, Irina (Folder 25: 3)
    - Megard, Irina (Folder 25: 4)
    - Mel'nikov, Aleksandr (Folder 25: 5)
    - Mengden, Irina, and Mariia (Folder 25: 6)
    - Men'shikov, Nikolai (Folder 25: 7)
    - Menzelintsev, Aleksandr (Folder 25: 8)
    - Merezhkovskii, Sergei (Folder 25: 9)
    - Merzheevskii, Aleksandr (Folder 25: 10)
    - Mesaksudi, Georgii, and Tat'iana, and Vladimir (Folder 25: 11)
    - Mesniankin, Viktor (Folder 25: 12)
    - Meshkov, Vladimir (Folder 25: 13)
    - Metal'nikov, Margarita, and Sergei (Folder 25: 14)
    - Miatura, Evgeniia (Folder 25: 15)
    - Migulin, Filip (Folder 25: 16)
    - Mikhailov, Andrei (Folder 25: 17)
    - Mikhailova, Lidiia, Zinaida (Folder 25: 18)
    - Mikhalevich, Aleksandr (Folder 25: 19)
    - Mikhal'chenko, Georgii, and Lidiia (Folder 25: 20)
    - Mikhevich-Ebner, Mariia (Folder 25: 21)
    - Milio, Irina (Folder 25: 22)
    - Miliukova, Anastasiia, Viktoriia (Folder 25: 23)
    - Miller, Elena (Folder 25: 24)
    - Miller, Iurii, Vsevolod (Folder 25: 25)
    - Miller, Lidiia, Sergei (Folder 25: 26)
    - Milobendskaia, Liudmila, and Tat'iana (Folder 25: 27)
    - Miloradovich, Ol'ga, and Serafim (Folder 25: 28)
    - Minash, Evgeniia (Folder 25: 29)
    - Minkevich, Ivan, and Ia. (Folder 25: 30)
    - Minkvits, Ol'ga, and Tat'iana, and Vera (Folder 25: 31)
    - Minn, Vladimir (Folder 25: 32)
    - Minor, Leonid, and Zinaida (Folder 25: 33)
    - Mirkovich, Elena (Folder 25: 34)
    - Mironova, Ariadna, and Lidiia (Folder 25: 35)
    - Miroskhedzhi, Aleksandr (Folder 25: 36)
    - Mishkalev, Aleksandr (Folder 25: 37)
    - Mishustova, Tamara (Folder 25: 38)
    - Misinov, Georgii (Folder 25: 39)
    - Mitrofanova, Tat'iana (Folder 25: 40)
    - Mkhitarov (Mkhitariants), Nikolai (Folder 25: 41)
    - Modrakh, Nataliia (Folder 25: 42)
    - Mokros, Mariia (Folder 25: 43)
    - Molchanov, Sergei (Folder 25: 44)
    - Molchevskii, Georgii, and Alla (Folder 25: 45)
    - Moller, Nikolai (Folder 25: 46)
    - Molodovskaia, Elena, and Tat'iana (Folder 25: 47)
    - Molodovskaia, Liudmila (Folder 25: 48)
    - Mordvintseva, Kseniia (Folder 25: 49)
    - Morozov, Marina, and Sergei (Folder 25: 50)
    - Morozov, Vladimir (Folder 25: 51)
    - Morozova, Mariia (Folder 25: 52)
    - Morozova, Mariia (Folder 25: 53)
    - Moskovchenko, Irina (Folder 25: 54)
    - Moskvin, Vadim (Folder 25: 55)
    - Mundirov, Nikolai (Folder 25: 56)
    - Mudrova, Svetlana (Folder 25: 57)
    - Mukhin, Igor' (Folder 25: 58)
    - Mukhin, Ivan (Folder 25: 59)
    - Murav'ev, Igor', and Lev, and Pavel (Folder 25: 60)
    - Murav'ev, Sergei (Folder 25: 61)
    - Muroz, Andrei (Folder 25: 62)
    - Muroz, M. (Folder 25: 63)
    - Musatov, Georgii (Folder 25: 64)
    - Mushkatina, Edia (Folder 25: 65)
    - Mussa-Baez, Elvrikh, and Emilio, and Patritsiia (Folder 25: 66)
    - Mussuri, Petr (Folder 25: 67)
    - Mutafov, Leonid (Folder 25: 68)
    - Mutavian, Levon (Folder 25: 69)
    - Mutius, Ekaterina, and Ivan, and Giselle (Folder 25: 70)
    - Mutulia, Ansel'm (Folder 25: 71)
    - Myslin, Mikhail, and Oleg, and Svetlana (Folder 25: 72)
    - Nabokov, Nikolai (Folder 25: 73)
    - Nasledysheva, Tat'iana (Folder 25: 74)
    - Naumov, Evgenii (Folder 25: 75)
    - Nabrotskii, Andrei, and Igor' (Folder 25: 76)
    - Nazarov, Boris (Folder 25: 77)
    - Nazarov, Iurii (Folder 25: 78)
    - Nedachina, Anna (Folder 25: 79)
    - Nefedov, Aleksandra, and Nikolai, and Tat'iana (Folder 25: 80)
    - Nekrasov, Aleksandr, Galina (Folder 25: 81)
    - Nekrasov, Aleksandr, Ol'ga (Folder 25: 82)
    - Nekrasov, Nikolai (Folder 25: 83)
    - Nelidova, Irina (Folder 25: 84)
    - Nemkov, Viktor (Folder 25: 85)
    - Nenarokov, Nikolai (Folder 25: 86)
    - Neniukova, Nina (Folder 25: 87)
    - Nepomniashchii, Aleksei, and Leonid (Box-folder 26: 1)
    - Nersenian, Seda (Folder 26: 2)
    - Neve, Patrick (Folder 26: 3)
    - Neviadomskaia, Irina, and Nataliia (Folder 26: 4)
    - Nikishin, Filip (Folder 26: 5)
    - Nikitin, Sergei (Folder 26: 6)
    - Nikitina, Ol'ga (Folder 26: 7)
    - Nikolaev, Vitalii (Folder 26: 8)
    - Nikolaeva, Ariadna (Folder 26: 9)
    - Nikolaeva, Liudmila (Folder 26: 10)
    - Nikonov, Gaii (Folder 26: 11)
    - Nikonov, Nikolai (Folder 26: 12)
    - Nikonov, Oleg (Folder 26: 13)
    - Nikol'skaia, Marina (Folder 26: 14)
    - Nikol'skii, Dimitrii (Folder 26: 15)
    - Nissen, Georgii (Folder 26: 16)
    - Noimis, Aleksandr (Folder 26: 17)
    - Novikov, Anatolii (Folder 26: 18)
    - Novitskii, Dimitrii (Folder 26: 19)
    - Novokreshchenova, Irina (Folder 26: 20)
    - Novosil'tsev, Georgii (Folder 26: 21)
    - Nozhin, Aleksandr (Folder 26: 22)
    - Numiss, Aleksandr (Folder 26: 23)
    - Obraztsov, Nina, Vladimir (Folder 26: 24)
    - Ochakovskii, Izrael (Folder 26: 25)
    - Ochkurova, Mariia (Folder 26: 26)
    - Odinets, Mikhail (Folder 26: 27)
    - Odoleev, Viktor (Folder 26: 28)
    - Ogneva, Tat'iana (Folder 26: 29)
    - Okhotnikov, Aleksandr (Folder 26: 30)
    - Okhotnikova, Ekaterina (Folder 26: 31)
    - Olekhonovich, Mariia, and Zinaida (Folder 26: 32)
    - Olovianishnikova, Vera (Folder 26: 33)
    - Ol'denburg, Elena, Ol'ga, Sergei (Folder 26: 34)
    - Ol'shevskaia, Tat'iana (Folder 26: 35)
    - Omirov, Leonid (Folder 26: 36)
    - Onachek, Asim (Folder 26: 37)
    - Ore, Evgenii (Folder 26: 38)
    - Oreik, Nikolai (Folder 26: 39)
    - Orlov, Aleksandr (Folder 26: 40)
    - Orlov, Mikhail (Folder 26: 41)
    - Orlov, Oleg (Folder 26: 42)
    - Orlovskii, Anna-Tat'iana, and Iurii (Folder 26: 43)
    - Orlov-Denisov, Georgii (Folder 26: 44)
    - Orzhil', Elizaveta (Folder 26: 45)
    - Osadchikova, Mariia (Folder 26: 46)
    - Osennii, Fedor (Folder 26: 47)
    - Osipov, Georgii (Folder 26: 48)
    - Oshanin, Kir (Folder 26: 49)
    - Osorgin, Mikhail, and Nikolai, and Sergei (Folder 26: 50)
    - Ostaptsev, Aleksandr, and Georgii (Folder 26: 51)
    - Osten-Saken, Aleksandra, and Ekaterina, and Vladimir (Folder 26: 52)
    - Ostopolov, Aleksei (Folder 26: 53)
    - Ovchinnikov, Oleg, and Suzanna (Folder 26: 54)
    - Ovchinnikov, Valentin (Folder 26: 55)
    - Ovgarenko, Igor' (Folder 26: 56)
    - Ovtrakht, Aleksandr, and Andrei, and Pavel (Folder 26: 57)
    - Ozeretskovskii, Mikhail (Folder 26: 58)
    - Pako, Sergei (Folder 26: 59)
    - Palashkovskii, Vsevolod (Folder 26: 60)
    - Palen, Anna, Sergei (Folder 26: 61)
    - Palii, Elena (Folder 26: 62)
    - Palimpsestova, Mariia (Folder 26: 63)
    - Panfilov, Aleksandr (Folder 26: 64)
    - Panfilova, Nataliia (Folder 26: 65)
    - Panfilova, Nina (Folder 26: 66)
    - Parskii, Aleksandr (Folder 26: 67)
    - Pashchenko, Militsa (Folder 26: 68)
    - Pashkevich, Andrei (Folder 26: 69)
    - Pashutin, Nikita (Folder 26: 70)
    - Pasko, Therry (Folder 26: 71)
    - Pasternak, Anatolii (Folder 26: 72)
    - Pasternatskii, Boris (Folder 26: 73)
    - Pavlov, A. (Folder 26: 74)
    - Pavlov, Aleksandr (Folder 26: 75)
    - Pavlov, Georgii, and Sergei (Folder 26: 76)
    - Pavlova, Tat'iana (Folder 26: 77)
    - Pelekhin, Petr (Folder 26: 78)
    - Pelekhina, Liubov' (Folder 26: 79)
    - Pelle, Oleg (Folder 26: 80)
    - Perebaskina, Liudmila, and Nataliia (Folder 26: 81)
    - Pereiaslavtsev, Mariia, and Mikhail, and Ol'ga (Box-folder 27: 1)
    - Perekotina, Ol'ga (Folder 27: 2)
    - Perel'man, Nina (Folder 27: 3)
    - Permiakova, Aleksandra (Folder 27: 4)
    - Pereverzev, Petr, and Tat'iana (Folder 27: 5)
    - Pershina, Nina (Folder 27: 6)
    - Perskaia, Mavra (Folder 27: 7)
    - Pertik, Nikolai (Folder 27: 8)
    - Petersen, Mr. (Folder 27: 9)
    - Petnograi, Odette (Folder 27: 10)
    - Petrenko, Viktor (Folder 27: 11)
    - Petrishchenko, Valentin (Folder 27: 12)
    - Petrosiuk, Nadezhda (Folder 27: 13)
    - Petrov, Aleksandr (Folder 27: 14)
    - Petrov, Aleksei, and Ivan, and Mikhail (Folder 27: 15)
    - Petrov, Andrei (Folder 27: 16)
    - Petrov, Mikhail (Folder 27: 17)
    - Petrov, Sergei (Folder 27: 18)
    - Petrova, Elena (Folder 27: 19)
    - Petrova, Nataliia (Folder 27: 20)
    - Petrova, Tat'iana (Folder 27: 21)
    - Petrovich, Boris, Vladimir (Folder 27: 22)
    - Petrovskii, Anatolii (Folder 27: 23)
    - Peunova, Liudmila (Folder 27: 24)
    - Pflieger, Joseph-Jules (Folder 27: 25)
    - Piatnitskii, Konstantin (Folder 27: 26)
    - Pimenova, Ekaterina (Folder 27: 27)
    - Pignon, Dominique (Folder 27: 28)
    - Pirra, Pavel (Folder 27: 29)
    - Pisarenko, Lidiia (Folder 27: 30)
    - Plagny, Iurii de (Folder 27: 31)
    - Plakhotnikova, Tat'iana (Folder 27: 32)
    - Plakhova, Elena (Folder 27: 33)
    - Plamenevskii, Sergei (Folder 27: 34)
    - Planida, Stefan (Folder 27: 35)
    - Plater, Kirill de (Folder 27: 36)
    - Pleshcheev, Vsevolod (Folder 27: 37)
    - Pleskovskaia, Ol'ga (Folder 27: 38)
    - Pliasova, Nataliia (Folder 27: 39)
    - Plontkovskii, Georgii (Folder 27: 40)
    - Plosskaia, Vera (Folder 27: 41)
    - Plotnikov, Nataliia, and Stefan (Folder 27: 42)
    - Poberezhskii, Boris (Folder 27: 43)
    - Podgornyi, Kirill (Folder 27: 44)
    - Podol'skii, Aleksandr, and Sergei (Folder 27: 45)
    - Podorvan, Tamara (Folder 27: 46)
    - Pogibin, Oleg (Folder 27: 47)
    - Pogoretskii, Aleksandr (Folder 27: 48)
    - Pogosian, Vagan (Folder 27: 49)
    - Pokrovskii, Aleksandra, and Irina, and Marina, and Sofiia (Folder 27: 50)
    - Poleshchuk, Boris (Folder 27: 51)
    - Poletika, Valentina (Folder 27: 52)
    - Polezhaeva, Nina (Folder 27: 53)
    - Poliakov, Anna, Sergei (Folder 27: 54)
    - Poliakova, Ekaterina (Folder 27: 55)
    - Poliakova, Irina (Folder 27: 56)
    - Polianovskaia, Tat'iana (Folder 27: 57)
    - Polianovskii, Georgii, Zinovii (Folder 27: 58)
    - Polianskaia, Nina (Folder 27: 59)
    - Politaev, Vladimir (Folder 27: 60)
    - Pomerantseva, Kira (Folder 27: 61)
    - Pomriaskinskaia, Evgeniia, and Tamara, and Viktoriia (Folder 27: 62)
    - Ponomarenko, Oleg (Folder 27: 63)
    - Ponomarenko, Ol'ga (Folder 27: 64)
    - Ponomarenko, Valentin (Folder 27: 65)
    - Ponomarev, E. (Folder 27: 66)
    - Ponomareva, Elena (Folder 27: 67)
    - Popenko, Nikifor (Folder 27: 68)
    - Popov, Aleksandr (Folder 27: 69)
    - Popov, Mikhail (Folder 27: 70)
    - Popov, Oleg (Folder 27: 71)
    - Popova, Elena (Folder 27: 72)
    - Popova, Galina (Folder 27: 73)
    - Popova, Liudmila (Folder 27: 74)
    - Popova, Marfa, Mariia, Vera (Folder 27: 75)
    - Popova, Nina (Folder 27: 76)
    - Poremskaia, Aleksei (Folder 27: 77)
    - Porkhonskii, S. (Folder 27: 78)
    - Porshe, Anna (Folder 27: 79)
    - Posokhov, Ms. (Folder 27: 80)
    - Potapova, Tamara (Folder 27: 81)
    - Potekina, Mariia, and Ol'ga, and Sofiia (Box-folder 28: 1)
    - Pozdnyshev, Ivan (Folder 28: 2)
    - Pozdnyshev, Petr (Folder 28: 3)
    - Pozdnyshev, Vladimir (Folder 28: 4)
    - Pozner, Georgii (Folder 28: 5)
    - Pozner, Viktor, and Vladimir (Folder 28: 6)
    - Pravatiner, Sofiia (Folder 28: 7)
    - Preobrazhenskii, Georgii, and Mikhail (Folder 28: 8)
    - Prikhnenko, Iurii, and Nina (Folder 28: 9)
    - Pikhod'ko, Georgii (Folder 28: 10)
    - Prikulenko, Roman (Folder 28: 11)
    - Primakov, Konstantin (Folder 28: 12)
    - Pritokhin-Petrov, Liudmila, and Mikhail, and Vera (Folder 28: 13)
    - Prizov, Anatolii (Folder 28: 14)
    - Prokhanov, Evgenii (Folder 28: 15)
    - Prokof'ev, Konstantin (Folder 28: 16)
    - Prokof'ev, Viktor (Folder 28: 17)
    - Prokof'eva, Elena (Folder 28: 18)
    - Prokopov-Orlovskii, Andrei (Folder 28: 19)
    - Prokushinskaia, Kseniia (Folder 28: 20)
    - Proskuriakov, Boris (Folder 28: 21)
    - Proskuriakov, Nikolai (Folder 28: 22)
    - Protopopova, Vera (Folder 28: 23)
    - Prozorovskii, Vadim (Folder 28: 24)
    - Prshelitsa, Izabella (Folder 28: 25)
    - Pukhliakova, Nadezhda, and Viviane-Ariadna (Folder 28: 26)
    - Pundik, Evgeniia, and Vera (Folder 28: 27)
    - Puzino, Lidiia (Folder 28: 28)
    - Prytkova, Irina, and Tat'iana (Folder 28: 29)
    - Pustaia, Ekaterina (Folder 28: 30)
    - Rabinovich, Iia, and Zel'dina (Folder 28: 31)
    - Rabov, Aleksandr (Folder 28: 32)
    - Radchenko, Andrei (Folder 28: 33)
    - Radishchev, Kira (Folder 28: 34)
    - Radkovich, Vladimir (Folder 28: 35)
    - Radushinskaia, Mariia, and Ol'ga (Folder 28: 36)
    - Raevskii, Ivan, and Nikolai (Folder 28: 37)
    - Raigevich, Milo (Folder 28: 38)
    - Raimist, Maika (Folder 28: 39)
    - Raitsin, Isidor (Folder 28: 40)
    - Rappoport, Valentin (Folder 28: 41)
    - Rat'kov-Rozhno, Georgii, and Roman (Folder 28: 42)
    - Rausch von Traubenberg, Aleksandr (Folder 28: 43)
    - Razamat, Leonid (Folder 28: 44)
    - Rednikin, Gennadii (Folder 28: 45)
    - Reformatskii, Nikolai (Folder 28: 46)
    - Reitenberg, Rita (Folder 28: 47)
    - Remmikh, Margarita (Folder 28: 48)
    - Rempel, Anna (Folder 28: 49)
    - Ren, Irina and Vladimir (Folder 28: 50)
    - Rennenkampf, Aleksandr, Vladimir (Folder 28: 51)
    - Rengarten, Aleksandr, Dimitrii (Folder 28: 52)
    - Repnin, Mikhail (Folder 28: 53)
    - Reutskii, Georgii (Folder 28: 54)
    - Revenko, Oleg (Folder 28: 55)
    - Reznikov, Sergei (Folder 28: 56)
    - Riabchikova, Elena (Folder 28: 57)
    - Riabinin, Georgii (Folder 28: 58)
    - Riabov, Vladimir (Folder 28: 59)
    - Riavushinskaia, P. (Folder 28: 60)
    - Riadovkina, Ol'ga (Folder 28: 61)
    - Riecks, Gladys Eugenie (Folder 28: 62)
    - Rikhter, Andrei (Folder 28: 63)
    - Rimmer, Anna (Folder 28: 64)
    - Rimmer, Liudmila (Folder 28: 65)
    - Rochefort, Claire-Noel (Folder 28: 66)
    - Rodionov, Pavel (Folder 28: 67)
    - Rodionova, Kseniia (Folder 28: 68)
    - Roginskii, Iosif (Folder 28: 69)
    - Rogovina, Margarita (Folder 28: 70)
    - Roibul, Tatiana (Folder 28: 71)
    - Roller, Frederik (Folder 28: 72)
    - Romanov, Aleksandr (Folder 28: 73)
    - Romanov, Aleksei, and Sergei (Folder 28: 74)
    - Romanov, Igor' (Folder 28: 75)
    - Romanov, Nikolai (Folder 28: 76)
    - Romanova, Raissa (Folder 28: 77)
    - Romanovskii, Georgii (Folder 28: 78)
    - Roop, Khristofor, and Nikolai (Folder 28: 79)
    - Ross, Georgii (Folder 28: 80)
    - Ross, Robert Livingston (Folder 28: 81)
    - Rotov, Vasilii (Folder 28: 82)
    - Rovere, Mireille (Box-folder 29: 1)
    - Rozanov, Sergei (Folder 29: 2)
    - Rozhkov, Stepan (Folder 29: 3)
    - Rozhinskii, Mr. (Folder 29: 4)
    - Rozen-Maier, Svetlana (Folder 29: 5)
    - Rozenfel'd, Nikolai (Folder 29: 6)
    - Rozina, Ol'ga (Folder 29: 7)
    - Ruban, Lev (Folder 29: 8)
    - Rubinov, Vladimir (Folder 29: 9)
    - Rudakova, Marina (Folder 29: 10)
    - Rudin, Iakov (Folder 29: 11)
    - Rudnev, Georgii, and Kira, and Liudmila (Folder 29: 12)
    - Rudneva, Nataliia (Folder 29: 13)
    - Rudov, Viktor, and Nina (Folder 29: 14)
    - Rukin, Andrei, and Sergei (Folder 29: 15)
    - Rybal'skii-Butevich, Nikolai (Folder 29: 16)
    - Rydzevskaia, Ol'ga (Folder 29: 17)
    - Ryshkov, Nikolai (Folder 29: 18)
    - Saaruni, Grant (Folder 29: 19)
    - Sadde, Aleksandr, and Andrei (Folder 29: 20)
    - Sadovskii, Aleksandr (Folder 29: 21)
    - Sagovskaia, Nina (Folder 29: 22)
    - Sakhadzhiev, Igor', Nina (Folder 29: 23)
    - Sakharov, Nil (Folder 29: 24)
    - Sakhno-Ustinovich, Aleksandr (Folder 29: 25)
    - Sal'berg, Margarita (Folder 29: 26)
    - Salishchev, Boris (Folder 29: 27)
    - Salomon, Heinz (Folder 29: 28)